module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'What year did the first mobile phones go on sale in the U.S.?',
    a: '1988',
    b: '1983',
    c: '1991',
    d: '1985',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The Burj Khalifa building in Dubai is the tallest building in the world. How tall is it?',
    a: '2357 ft',
    b: '3413 ft',
    c: '1999 ft',
    d: '2717 ft',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Austin hasn\'t always been called Austin. What was its name before it was called Austin?',
    a: 'Stephenville',
    b: 'Waterloo',
    c: 'San Austin',
    d: 'Shoal Creek Settlement',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which U.S. president was the first to declare a "war on drugs"?',
    a: 'Richard Nixon',
    b: 'Ronald Reagan',
    c: 'Gerald Ford',
    d: 'Jimmy Carter',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What was the first car intended for public sale that had an airbag?',
    a: '1977 Pontiac Trans Am',
    b: '1981 Lincoln Town Car',
    c: '1973 Oldsmobile Toronado',
    d: '1975 AMC Pacer',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What Texas city was the first H.E.B (C.C. Butt Grocery Store) opened?',
    a: 'Kerrville',
    b: 'Austin',
    c: 'Laredo',
    d: 'Del Rio',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'If driving a car on a race track and you have a long straight after a sharp corner, you\'re best strategy is to...',
    a: 'early apex the corner',
    b: 'drift the corner',
    c: 'late apex the corner',
    d: 'close your eyes and hope for the best',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'How long did it take the SR-71 Blackbird to fly from the West Coast to the East Coast (2,404 miles)?',
    a: '2 hr 01 min',
    b: '1 hr 29 min',
    c: '1 hr 41 min',
    d: '1 hr 07 min',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'How many states are there that do not observe daylight savings?',
    a: '4',
    b: '3',
    c: '2',
    d: '1',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What did the 18th Amendment to the Constitution do?',
    a: 'gave women the right to vote',
    b: 'banned the manufacture and sale of intoxicating liquor',
    c: 'limited the President to two terms',
    d: 'outlawed slavery',
    answer: 'b'
  },
];